Statistical Jokes and Social Effects | Pages: 294-300 (7 pages)
Synthetic DiD and Regression Discontinuity | Pages: 625-646 (22 pages)
The synthetic control method | Pages: 187-212 (26 pages)
Causal Invariance in Reasoning and Learning | Pages: 287-325 (39 pages)
Learning symmetric causal independence models | Pages: 133-153 (21 pages)
Causal discovery with a mixture of DAGs | Pages: 4201-4225 (25 pages)
Empirical Inference of Numerical Information into Causal Strategy Models by Means of Artificial Intelligence | Pages: 283-303 (21 pages)
Completing causal networks by meta-level abduction | Pages: 239-277 (39 pages)
A Reply to Cohen's Book Review of Creating a Memory of Causal Relationships | Pages: 185-190 (6 pages)
A reply to Cohen's book review of Creating a Memory of Causal Relationships | Pages: 185-190 (6 pages)
Learning causal patterns: Making a transition from data-driven to theory-driven learning | Pages: 173-194 (22 pages)
Learning Causal Patterns: Making a Transition from Data-Driven to Theory-Driven Learning | Pages: 173-194 (22 pages)
Causal Domain Generalization | Pages: 161-185 (25 pages)
Creating a memory of causal relationships, by Michael Pazzani, Hillsdale, NJ: Lawrence Erlbaum, 1990 | Pages: 179-183 (5 pages)
Book Review: Creating a Memory of Causal Relationships, by Michael Pazzani. Hillsdale, NJ: Lawrence Erlbaum, 1990 | Pages: 179-183 (5 pages)
Least-squares independence regression for non-linear causal inference under non-Gaussian noise | Pages: 249-267 (19 pages)
Causal Inference and Recommendations | Pages: 207-245 (39 pages)
Causal Inference and Natural Language Processing | Pages: 189-206 (18 pages)
On the benefits of representation regularization in invariance based domain generalization | Pages: 895-915 (21 pages)
Causal Inference on Graphs | Pages: 53-78 (26 pages)
Causal Explainable AI | Pages: 137-159 (23 pages)
Continual Causal Effect Estimation | Pages: 283-295 (13 pages)
Causal Trees and Forests | Pages: 544-581 (38 pages)
Causal Effect Estimation: Recent Progress, Challenges, and Opportunities | Pages: 79-100 (22 pages)
Causal Discovery | Pages: 159-159 (1 pages)
Using causal discovery for feature selection in multivariate numerical time series | Pages: 377-395 (19 pages)
